magforwomen.com 2014-11-22

# Privacy Policy - Mag For Women

We respect the privacy of our visitors and surfers. We use Facebook and Twitter to increase your interaction with our website using these social media tools. We do not have access to your these accounts in any way. We do not store any information about what articles you read on the website.

Limitations on privacy:  
We reserve the right to provide information if we think – correctly or incorrectly and reasonably or unreasonably – that our content, is being used in violation of our terms of use, including, but not limited to, being used in any illegal, harmful, threatening or anti-social activity.

We try to protect your privacy, but you must please understand that any use of the Internet or of email creates the possibility that someone could access the data transmitted. There is always some risk on the web that personal information might be accessed and privacy cannot be guaranteed.

Affiliates, Advertisers and Others:  
Before providing information to any party other than magforwomen.com, you should check their privacy policy, as they are third parties. We are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices utilized by any other sites, linked by us.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this website. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

These Swimming Pools are some of the most amazing you will find in the world. If you get lucky sometime, do take a nice dip. Cheers!

#### 1.Jade Mountain Resort, St Lucia

#### 2.St Regis, Tibet

#### 3 Crocosaurus Cove, Australia

#### 4.Cambrian Hotel, Switzerland

#### 5.Bay of Kotor

#### 6.Golden Triangle Resort, Thailand

#### 7.Hotel Hacienda, Spain

#### 8.Gellert Baths, Budapest, Hungary

#### 9.Udaipur, India

#### 10.Amazing pool at Hearst Castle

#### 11.Library Pool Koh Samui

#### 12.Hotel Caruso Ravello Italy

#### 13.Marina Bay Sands, Singapore

#### 14.Devils Pool, Victoria Fall

A guy decided to make a natural swimming pool in his backyard. And it looks like a forest pond. There are no chemicals in the water. Everything is eco-friendly. Check out how he did it.

Holly Spring’s daughter has one hand due to Hirschsprung’s Disease from an early age. Holly happens to be an award winning photographer from New Zealand. She tried to encourage her daughter to follow her dreams by clicking beautiful photos of her. Her work will inspire one and all. Have a look. Also like her on Facebook

Jessica Vigansky’s dad was waiting to hear the good news from his daughter. When he finally heard it, his daughter recorded and posted his reaction on Youtube. Watch the beautiful moment in this family’s life.

These paths in the midst of natural beauty are the most beautiful you will find in the world. Just looking at these pictures makes me dreamy. 

#### Hitachi Seaside Park Path In Japan

#### Rhododendron Tunnel in Reenagross Park, Kenmare Ireland

#### Jacaranda Tree Alley

#### Spring In Spencer Smith Park, Burlington, Ontario, Canada

#### Path Up To The Halnaker Windmill in Sussex, UK

#### Forest Path In Autumn

#### Forest Trail In Bavaria, Germany

#### Autumn Path In Kyoto, Japan

#### Winter Forest Path, Czech Republic

#### Migliarino San Rossore Park Path In Pisa, Italy

#### Autumn Path

#### Cotton Tree Alley In Taiwan

#### Spring In Hallerbos Forest, Belgium

#### Dark Hedges In Ireland

#### Bamboo Path In Kyoto, Japan

#### Russian Forest Path

#### Path Up To The Halnaker Windmill in Sussex, UK

#### Winter Sunrise On Path In Campigna National Park , Italy

#### Spring In Woodburn, Oregon, USA

#### Taiping Mountain Path in Taiwan

Share these magical pathways with your friends around the world.

I love when I see people who help others. When this helpless turtle gets rescued by Colin Sutton & Cameron Dietrich, he swims away happily. The end moments will make you fill with joy.

The fun starts when this Parakeet starts speaking. This bird should become a Hollywood movie star. He will mint money with his cool voice and style.

Watch this video. Can you guess why the bride became furious after watching this video? here it is -

[Monica {+} Felix – Wedding Video](http://vimeo.com/56542431) from [Visualaz](http://vimeo.com/visualaz) on [Vimeo](https://vimeo.com/).
